<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ethan Vu</title>
    <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ethan Vu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Ethan Vu, Dan Weru, and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 09:32:17 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ethanvu.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Polygoneer (2017) Review</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/polygoneer-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 09:32:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/polygoneer-2017/</guid>
      <description>Playing Polygoneer makes me think of John Wick hunting the Russian kid in the nightclub from the first film. Shooting at bad guys coming from all sides with pretty shapes, colors, and a bumpin’ soundtrack in the background. Polygoneer lacks the excitement that John Wick (2014) has however.
Unlocking stages is extremely easy. There are world leaderboards for each level, but they don’t get harder the longer one survives. At least I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to see one because I typically end my runs after 90-ish seconds due to the monotony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 and the Rally Round the Flag Effect</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/politics/rally-rona-flag-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 03:14:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/politics/rally-rona-flag-effect/</guid>
      <description>Alternative title: The Rally Rona Flag Effect The purpose of this post is to expand on this interesting tweet I saw: https://twitter.com/leonardocarella/status/1243648800872443904
What is the &amp;ldquo;rally round the flag effect&amp;rdquo;? In the US, it&amp;rsquo;s basically an event that draws Americans together to support the President. John E. Mueller said such events must 1) be international, 2) involve the United States and the President, and 3) is specific, dramatic, and sharply focused in his 1970 paper Presidential Popularity from Truman to Johnson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing ALOT, ALOV, MEUITM, and other mods for Mass Effect on Linux</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-games-on-linux/modding-mass-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 14:25:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-games-on-linux/modding-mass-effect/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Valve&amp;rsquo;s Proton allows Steam users to run games that don&amp;rsquo;t have a native Linux implementation on their Linux machines. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing. Mass Effect is has a Gold rating on ProtonDB which means it runs well when using Proton, with minor adjustments. If you have the game on Origin or you have a physical copy, you can also play on Linux, but you&amp;rsquo;ll have to use Lutris or something similar instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cook, Serve, Delicious! (2012) Review</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/cook-serve-delicious-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:25:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/cook-serve-delicious-2012/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I bought a mechanical keyboard for $150 and a coworker was surprised when I told him. He asked why I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get an office keyboard for a tenth of the price. Clearly he&amp;rsquo;s never beaten Cook, Serve, Delicious! on extreme difficulty or else he would know.
For each tug at a wine&amp;rsquo;s cork, each pounding of a tenderizer onto a chicken breast, each ingredient added to a salad bowl, there is visceral feedback, both audio and touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Ratings Reference</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 21:52:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/ratings/</guid>
      <description>Here I&amp;rsquo;ll describe the buckets that I put games into for how much I enjoyed them.
There are eight in total, numbered 0 to 7, which is unconventional, but I feel that is just the optimal number of buckets. Most video game reviewers that apply ratings to the games usually use a 10-point scale but don&amp;rsquo;t utilize the lower end anyway.
0 These are worst games of all time. They are unique in how offensively bad they are.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>