<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>video game reviews on Ethan Vu</title>
    <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/categories/video-game-reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in video game reviews on Ethan Vu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Ethan Vu, Dan Weru, and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 02:22:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ethanvu.github.io/categories/video-game-reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call of Duty: Warzone (2020) Review</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/call-of-duty-warzone-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 02:22:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/call-of-duty-warzone-2020/</guid>
      <description>In typical Call of Duty multiplayer modes, kills and deaths are meaningless. Respawn timers are as fast as one is able to hit the F key and scoreboards hide death counters until the end of matches. The game is so fast paced, there’s not much time for long term planning. It’s not like most folks have a plan anyway. I have a 1.33 win/loss ratio despite a 0.99 kill/death ratio simply because I’m the only player haphazardly throwing my body onto objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mass Effect (2007) Review</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/mass-effect-2007/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 02:51:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/mass-effect-2007/</guid>
      <description>One of the most harrowing thoughts is that we humans might be all alone in the Universe. When the Sun inevitably devours Earth, will there be no one left to experience the world and create stories? BioWare imagines a galaxy where the answer is NO in Mass Effect. This galaxy is buzzing with life and adventure. It’s rife with conflict and problems, but they’re not unsolvable. In fact, they’re waiting to be solved… by the right person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polygoneer (2017) Review</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/polygoneer-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 09:32:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/polygoneer-2017/</guid>
      <description>Playing Polygoneer makes me think of John Wick hunting the Russian kid in the nightclub from the first film. Shooting at bad guys coming from all sides with pretty shapes, colors, and a bumpin’ soundtrack in the background. Polygoneer lacks the excitement that John Wick (2014) has however.
Unlocking stages is extremely easy. There are world leaderboards for each level, but they don’t get harder the longer one survives. At least I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to see if they did get any more difficult because I typically end my runs after 90-ish seconds due to the monotony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cook, Serve, Delicious! (2012) Review</title>
      <link>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/cook-serve-delicious-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:25:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ethanvu.github.io/post/video-game-reviews/cook-serve-delicious-2012/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I bought a mechanical keyboard for $150 and a coworker was surprised when I told him. He asked why I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get an office keyboard for a tenth of the price. Clearly he&amp;rsquo;s never beaten Cook, Serve, Delicious! on extreme difficulty or else he would know.
For each tug at a wine&amp;rsquo;s cork, each pounding of a tenderizer onto a chicken breast, each ingredient added to a salad bowl, there is visceral feedback, both audio and touch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>